(Raj:)Hey.
- Sorry we're late.
- Hey.
(Penny:)No problem. We just sat down.
- Mm. Would you like some wine?
- Fill her up.
(Bernadette:)I'll tell you when to stop.
(Penny:)Is everything okay?
(Howard:)Terrific. Couldn't be better.
(Bernadette:)Oh, bite me.
(Howard:)We can still have a nice night.
Just tell me where it is.
(Bernadette:)If you did what you said
you were gonna do, I'd tell you.
- Uh, where what is?
- She hid my Xbox like I'm a child.
(Howard:)My mom got me that for my birthday,
so if you don't give it back, I'm telling.
(Bernadette:)I've been working late every night.
All I asked was he clean the apartment...
(Bernadette:)...and do one load of laundry.
Did he? No.
He kept on playing
that stupid game.
(Bernadette:)You like pushing buttons so much,
try pushing them on the washing machine.
- I said I'm sorry.
- Sorry doesn't clean my underpants, buddy.